<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">LovelaceNeumann</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="Ada_Lovelace">Ada Lovelace</string>
    <string name="caption_ada">Augusta Ada King, Countess of Lovelace (10 December 1815 – 27 November 1852), born Augusta Ada Byron 
	and now commonly known as Ada Lovelace, was an English mathematician and writer chiefly known for her work
	on Charles Babbage\'s early mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine. Her notes on the engine
	include what is recognised as the first algorithm intended to be carried out by a machine. 
	Because of this, she is often described as the worlds first computer programmer.</string>
    <string name="picture_of_ada_lovelace">Picture of Ada LoveLace</string>
    <string name="John_Von_Neumann">John Von Neumann</string>
    <string name="picture_of_Johon_von_neumann">Picture of Johon Von Neumann</string>
    <string name="caption_jhon">
    John von Neumann (December 28, 1903 – February 8, 1957) was a Hungarian-American pure and applied mathematician and polymath.
	He made major contributions to a number of fields,including mathematics (foundations of mathematics, functional analysis, 
	ergodic theory, geometry, topology, and numerical analysis), physics (quantum mechanics, hydrodynamics, and fluid dynamics), 
	economics (game theory), computer science (Von Neumann architecture, linear programming, self-replicating machines, 
	stochastic computing), and statistics.He was a pioneer of the application of operator theory to quantum mechanics, 
	in the development of functional analysis, a principal member of the Manhattan Project and the Institute for Advanced Study 
	in Princeton (as one of the few originally appointed), and a key figure in the development of game theory and the concepts of 
	cellular automata,[1] the universal constructor, and the digital computer.</string>
    
</resources>
